sfm-offshore.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy

Effective Date : 06/12/2013 

This privacy policy applies to [http://www.sfm-offshore.com](http://www.sfm-offshore.com/index.html), owned and operated by SFM Corporate Services (“SFM”, “We”, “Us”) This privacy policy describes how SFM collects and uses the personal information you provide on our website. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

SFM Corporate Services has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/), including transparency, accountability and choice, regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website [http://www.sfm-offshore.com](http://www.sfm-offshore.com/index.html). It does not cover information collected on the foreign-language domains owned and operated by SFM Corporate Services. It also does not cover information that may be collected offline. 

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organisations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy1914%20=%20'info'%20+%20'@';%20addy1914%20=%20addy1914%20+%20'sfm-offshore'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy1914%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy1914%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[info@sfm-offshore.com](mailto:info@sfm-offshore.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request) here. 

## 1\. Information Collection and Use

We collect the following personal information from you: 

  * Contact Information, such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number.
  * Billing Information, such as credit card number and billing address.
  * Information about your business, such as company name, address, business type.

We may collect the personal information of third parties when you add the names of shareholders or beneficiaries on our order forms. Collection of third party personally identifiable information may be necessary to process and register your order for certain products or services. We will not use this information for any other commercial purpose. These third parties may contact us at [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy79442%20=%20'info'%20+%20'@';%20addy79442%20=%20addy79442%20+%20'sfm-offshore'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy79442%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy79442%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[info@sfm-offshore.com](mailto:info@sfm-offshore.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

We use this information to: 

  * fulfill your order;
  * send you an order confirmation;
  * assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products;
  * send you requested a product or information;
  * respond to customer service requests;
  * send you communications;
  * conduct due diligence; and
  * respond to your questions and concerns.

## 2\. Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

### Service Providers

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing your order/payment, registering your business or offering customer service. These companies are authorised to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services. 

### Frames

Some of our pages utilise framing techniques to serve content to from our service providers (such as a payment processor) while preserving the look and feel of our site. Please be aware that you are providing your personal information to these third parties and not to [http://www.sfm-offshore.com](http://www.sfm-offshore.com/index.html). 

### Legal Disclaimer

We may also disclose your personal information: 

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;
  * if SFM is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information; ans
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

## 3\. User Access and Choice

If your personal information changes, you may correct, update, amend or delete it by emailing our Customer Support at [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy85556%20=%20'info'%20+%20'@';%20addy85556%20=%20addy85556%20+%20'sfm-offshore'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy85556%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy85556%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[info@sfm-offshore.com](mailto:info@sfm-offshore.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below or on the [Contact Us](http://www.sfm-offshore.com/contact-offshorecompanymanagementspecialists.html) page. We will respond to your request within 30 days. If you have a Corporate Service Officer assigned, please contact him/her in priority. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. If you request that we delete your personal information, we will notify you if we are unable to do so and why. 

### Opt-out Preferences

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter on the main site or when you become an SFM customer, we will use your name and email address to send you non-transactional, promotional emails from time to time. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving these emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can [contact us](http://www.sfm-offshore.com/contact-offshorecompanymanagementspecialists.html). 

## 4\. Tracking Technologies / Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies to track user behavior and to save information you put in our forms. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited. 

### Web Beacons/Gifs

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

### Analytics / Log Files

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyse trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. 

The use of tracking technologies by our service providers, technology partners or other third party assets (such as those involved in tracking the success of advertising) on the site is not covered by our privacy policy. These third parties may use cookies, clear gifs, images and scripts to help them better manage their content on our site. We do not have access or control over these technologies. We do not tie the information gathered to our customers’ or users’ personally identifiable information. 

### Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web Beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/).

Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

## 5\. Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card, bank account or proprietary business information) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).   
We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy519%20=%20'info'%20+%20'@';%20addy519%20=%20addy519%20+%20'sfm-offshore'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy519%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy519%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[info@sfm-offshore.com](mailto:info@sfm-offshore.com). 

## 6\. Additional Information

### Links to Third Party Sites

Our site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of SFM. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit. 

### Social Media Widgets

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons and widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it 

###  Testimonials

We may display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. These testimonials are pulled from a third party service provider, which may ask for your personal information, including your name and email address. Though we do not post the personally identifiable information to our site, if you wish to update or delete your testimonial, please contact the data controller. 

### Changes to This Policy

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

## 7\. Contact Us

SFM Corporate Services SA   
15, Rue du Cendrier   
1201 Geneva 

+41 22 311 03 83   
[ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy39834%20=%20'info'%20+%20'@';%20addy39834%20=%20addy39834%20+%20'sfm-offshore'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy39834%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy39834%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[info@sfm-offshore.com](mailto:info@sfm-offshore.com)
